Thank you for watching!
Thanks for your work!
We are very happy to have you as our guest on Halo! This time we have Morning Musume。' 23's Sei Fukumura and,
I'd like to introduce you to these two girls.
I would like to introduce you to these two,
Please stay with us until the end.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Now, Morning Musume。 23 and Ochanoma have performed together at the winter tour and Hima Fest,
How was it?
Yes, it was great. I learned a lot from Morning Musume。 23 taught me a lot of things,
I think I was able to absorb a lot of things by seeing them up close on stage.
It was a fun tour where we learned a lot from each other.
I also had the impression that there were many members who became good friends.
I also got to hang out with Maruka Saito in private,
I also had the chance to hang out with Maruka Saito in private, so I was happy about that as well.
Morning Musume。 23 is currently in the middle of its spring tour.
I think we just finished the first half of the tour,
We are going to Miyagi, Osaka, Shizuoka, Okayama, and Saitama during Golden Week.
We are very happy to be able to go to various places like this,
And after all, this is the 25th anniversary of Morning Musume。 25th anniversary,
I'm very happy to be going to various places like this, and also to be able to enjoy the history of Morning Musume,
I am very happy to be able to enjoy the moment with my fans while feeling the history of Morning Musume。
And, you know, on April 30, between tours, I will be performing with Airi Suzuki of Angelem at the Rocking On Presents Japan Jazz Festival.
I will also be performing at the Rocking On Presents Japan Jam 2023 with Ms. Airi Suzuki of Angulum.
I will be participating in the same event as last year, and I hope to make it a great success.
And Ocha-no-Oma will start its spring tour on May 3.
We will have concerts in Kanagawa Prefecture on May 3, Aichi Prefecture on May 6, and Osaka on May 21.
This will be the second tour, so I hope to show you a more improved version of Ocha-no-Oma.
Before that, I will be performing at the Hello Project Trainees' Presentation 2023 Spring Open Proficiency Test.
I will do my best. Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Please take a look at this video first. Please take a look.
Forge
The timing of hanging up the phone.
When love is over, that feeling...
I already know that feeling. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
For example, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's only there in the usual places.
Ugh.
It's not popular, but it's my favorite zone.
That's why it's okay to sing.
Come on, let's go have some fun.
Let's talk.
SISTAR No one understands me.
We're not cheap.
You know, if we'd been paying attention...
SISTAR What's happening to Nekki in the city
Glitter for us.
WOW!
Let it shine.
Come on!
Tin-Tana
Let's match and live
It's all wet and dyed
It's so good!
Ooh, ooh, ooh
Though the night wind blows
but it doesn't seem to cool down
Lissmosis
On someone's chest
I have to do something
I feel it in my heart
but
I was worried about myself
Shutters
should be the color of the match
Prafira for us
Burning on and on
Let it shine
In truth, you too
Instead of aiming for perfection
Be your absolute self
I'd rather wait for you
Hey, are you ready?
One, two, three, four!
Laugh with me tonight, cry with me tonight, laugh with me tonight
I'm so happy I'm not cheap
Look, they're all over my face.
I've cried in someone's heart before
But you've been troubled by your own problems
Taste and leeks, people are oursTaste and onions, people are ours
Hare no Kirakira, Burning on Fire
I hope it shines brightly
Thank you for everything!
Morning Musume。 I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer in a quick tempo.
Kirara Yonemura will turn 19 on April 30, so what do you want to accomplish in your teenage years?
What is the most important thing for you when you perform at events?
If you could have a holiday weekend like Golden Week, how would you like to spend it?
What is your make-up speciality? Raising my eyelashes!
What is your current goal for Ochanoma?
Wow, you're fast! Excellent!
I don't think that's what you mean.
I'd like to mention a few things that caught my attention... What do you want to accomplish as a teenager?
I want to go to Pilates... because I feel like I don't have enough muscles in my body.
I want to build up my muscles.
I don't know if I can do it or not, but I think it's really great that you can realize it while you're still in your teens.
I don't know if I can do it or not, but I notice it when I'm in my 20s and it's getting a little too much for me.
I see... I see... I think it's great that you can realize that while you're still in your 18s.
Please do it, and I'll make it happen!
I'll make it happen. I'm also very particular about my eyelashes.
Eyelashes. I do a lot of eyelash lifting.
There's a hot brower that raises lashes with heat, and I always set it to 80 degrees.
I set the temperature at 80 degrees Celsius all the time.
So you don't perm your eyelashes or anything like that, but you do it yourself every time?
Well, it's easier to raise them if they're not permed.
No, they're always shaggy. They look really beautiful from the side.
So you're really particular about it. I use about five mascaras.
That's great. That's great.
I'll always do my best on my own Thank you
We'll talk about your question after the VTR.
Talk to me
me
4Onsen Irushin GroupI can't even draw a dream in the night sky...
Angulum New Album Big Love
Now on sale!
Halo! STE!
I would like to ask Mr. Fukumura some questions. Please give me your best regards.
You have been uploading training videos on Instagram.
My stomach!
You have been addicted to pudding for the past six months.
Smoothness, bitter caramel, and overall atmosphere.
Oooh! What is something you would like to challenge yourself with?
I would like to learn to play the drums.
What is your favorite hair arrangement you often do for this spring tour?
To change the image of the first half and the second half.
This year marks the 25th anniversary of Morning Musume。 is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year. How would you describe Morning Musume。 In one word, how would you describe Morning Musume。
It is a form of love.
Thank you very much.
First of all, I was wondering about the pudding, do you like bitter caramel?
I like bitter. Pudding is sweet, isn't it?
It is sweet.
So I want the bitterness to wrap around the sweetness.
Oh, I see.
It depends on the type of pudding. Some have more sugar, some have more coffee, and so on,
Does it contain coffee?
There are puddings with so much sugar and coffee in them, that there are people who are particular about them.
I think the atmosphere is very important because it is fun and I see a lot of puddings.
I think the puddings in retro stores are bitter, aren't they?
I think most of them were bitter.
That's for sure.
I also think that most of the ones you can get at convenience stores have sweet caramel.
I have only had sweet pudding, but I would like to try it.
Please give it a try.
One more thing. One more thing about Morning Musume。 In one word, how would you describe Morning Musume。
A form of love.
It's wonderful.
I don't know what else to say,
I can't say anything else, but I can say that it is a form of love that has been passed down from seniors to juniors for 25 years,
And the juniors who carry on with the feelings of their seniors,
There are some members whose activities do not overlap with those of their seniors,
Some of the members have not been active in the group for 25 years, but they still love Morning Musume。 I think it's a way of passing on the feeling of the seniors to the younger members,
I also remember the time when I was a fan of Morning Musume。 I think that I will always keep those feelings in mind as I continue to be a member of the group,
I hope that the group will continue to do so for the next 30 to 40 years,
I hope that the group will continue to do so for the next 30 or 40 years.
I hope the group will continue to do so for 30 or 40 years.
I will do my best so that we can be a group that continues for a long time as adults.
I look forward to seeing you soon.
Halo! Ste will continue after this.
This is Nanami Kubota from Tea Horse. I am very excited that it is finally completed.My name is Nanami Kubota from Ocha-no-Ma. I am very excited to hear that it is finally finished.
What are you making today?
Today I'm making pasta with bacon and mushrooms in tomato sauce.
Looks delicious.
Is it heavy?
No, it's not heavy. I didn't do it on purpose.
This may be really heavy.
If you don't put enough salt here, it won't taste good.
You know that?
I know that. This much.
I know this much. As a pasta lover.
May I put it in?
Yes, you can.
In fact, if you put one percent, it might be too salty.
It's a little bit salty, but it's very salty.
You taste it?
Yes, I do.
Salt water
Yes, yes, yes.
It's the saltiness, the saltiness.
Salty? Salty?
Salty.
Oh, my God.
Is it salty?
No, it's not salty.
It's like salt?
It's like salt.
Should I leave it out?
Maybe a little.
A little bit.
One more time.
Okay, then.
Here we go. Here we go.
That's enough.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I dip it in salt and eat it.
Vegetables?
That's okay.
I'm fine.
This one...
This is a little...
Okay, let's do this.
When you put the pasta in...
The pasta absorbs the water.
The pasta itself doesn't have much saltiness.
So if you don't add saltiness here...
If you don't add salt, the pasta will be tasteless.
I understand.
It's okay.
Okay, that's what I was looking forward to the most.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll be back in a minute.
I'm just gonna practice a little bit.
Okay.
Here you go.
You should definitely use this.
Like this.
Let go.
Poof! Let go!
Oh!
You're good at that.
I did it.
I probably came here today for this.
Soon.
I'm nervous.
I'm so nervous.
It's nine minutes. That's the amount of time it says on the box.
So, eight minutes.
Yes, sir.
I divided it up.
I'll stop once.
Okay, ready?
Here you go.
Ha!
Whoo!
You did it!
You're so good!You're so good!
If you're watching this, you're going to love me now.
It's got to be a little bumpy.
I can't get the clay in.
Maybe once every couple of minutes or so.
Give it a stir.
And while you're at it, let's chop up some parsley.
Okay. Squeeze.
More. Do you want me to do it with the tip?
Oh, it's sharp. It's sharp.
That's good. I think I'm a genius.
I'm kind of googling it.
Ugh.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
One minute left, so just give it a little stir.
I can already tell by the way it's pulling together.
I think it's probably okay.
I'm gonna try it.
It's hot. It's hot.
No scene?
It's just a little bit, right?
A little bit. Okay, then.
Oh, my God.
You don't even have pliers.
A little of this boiling water.
Wow.
Here you go.
It's too thick to mix with pasta.
Ahhh...
Before Ochanomaru was formed, there was a trainee unit,
We had a sleepover party.
We had a sleepover party, and we decided to make a giant omelette.
No one else could cook, but I was the best at it, and I cut the whole thing by myself.
I couldn't stand to watch it. I thought to myself, "This is really not good.
I thought to myself, "If I think like that, I can do it.
I was a bit surprised at how long it takes to make a caster.
I didn't know it took this long to make a caster.
I made the tomato sauce from scratch.
Cool!
Isn't it good enough?
Serve it up.
Now and then.
Is this right? Yes, yes, yes.
I'm already getting involved.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, pull that one out.
Yes, yes, yes.
Maybe it's good.
It shines with the lighting. It's good. It's good, it's good, it's good.
It's good.
Plenty is good. It melts away pretty well.
I see. More and more.
I'm going to say, "Wow.
I think it's good.
It's done. Yay!
It's done!
Yay!
The pasta is shining so brightly, and it looks beautiful with green and other colors.
I'm going to eat it.
The rich tomatoes, the bacon and garlic, and the oil from frying the bacon and garlic are all in there, and it's really tasty.
It's really delicious, with a lot of flavor from the bacon and garlic, and the oil from the frying.
The garlic and other things you can't see, but I thought it was important to do a lot of detailed work.
I think you have a good sense of presentation and this pasta is very well done. I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
I think you should practice all over the place.
Thank you very much for today. Thank you very much.
I'm so hungry. I'm starving.
I want pasta. I want pasta.
I've appeared at Hello Kitchen before, and I made a pork gruyere for the show
They have everything you need in their kitchen room.
I made a marinade that was so delicious that I did it again at home.
I made a marinade that was so delicious that we did it again at home.
I learned a lot from this.
Kiraru, do you usually cook at home? I made stir-fried vegetables the other day.
I was able to make it, but the taste was a little lacking.
Something was missing. Something was missing?
But I can't tell by myself, so I'd like to participate in Hello Kitchen someday and improve my skills.
I'd like to improve my skills. You teach me well.
You teach me well, so even if I can't do something, I'll be able to do it.
I really want to participate. Let's participate.
I'd like that very much.
Hello! I'll be there.Hallo! STE!
Next is the lyrics presentation that touched my heart!
There are many songs in Hello! Project has many songs, but I love Tsubaki Factory's "What time is it?
I especially love the lyrics "Look at me, rather than words or attitude" at the beginning of the interlude.
I don't know why, but sometimes I can relate to it.
Tsubaki's music touches your heart, doesn't it? They resonate with me.
It can be a bit painful, but I really like that.
I understand.
By the way, there's a song by S/mileage called "Heavenly Snake", and in the last chorus, the lyrics are "I'm not interested in everything, you're going to move soon, don't be nice to me any more, I'll make you lie and cry"...
I really like that lyric. It's so cute.
It's so cute! I thought it was cute. It's really cute.
I've loved it for a long time now, but it's just so resonant that I can't understand it.
It's all about the heavenly serpent
All of them are heavenly snakes.
Now please watch the VTR.
Go ahead.
A presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart
In this corner, we will present lyrics from Hello! Project's songs that have touched our hearts and talk about their charms.
You, the viewers of "Hello! Project songs and talk about their charms!
This week, I, Honoka Kobayashi, will present the lyrics.
Here we go!
When we work hard, we work together
It's a line from the song "Fure Fure Everyday" by Beyonce.
I love the lyrics of this song the most, and I think it's great to listen to it simply.
I think it's great to listen to it simply, and the time before and after the lyrics are also very good.
When they sing the lyrics, they say, "When we work hard, we're all in this together.
Everyone sings with the same gesture, so you can sing along while listening to the song.
You can sing along while listening to the song.
It's different from the lyrics that say "hang in there" or "let's hang in there".
It's like Beyonce is doing her best with me.
I chose these lyrics because I thought they were reassuring.
I like that she's not cheering them on.
It's not about "hang in there" or "let's hang in there".
If there's ever a time to hang in there, we'll be with you.
Yes! I know! I know!
Let's not hang in there now. Let's hang in there when we can.
We'll be there for you when you need us.
Everyone in Beyonce is always like that.
Whenever there is something tough or challenging
Whenever we have a challenge or a hardship, they say, "Let's do our best together.
I feel like the members of Beyonce are the kind of people who say to you
I like the lyrics because I think they are perfect for Beyonce.
Yes, that's how I feel.
See you next time!
Hello! STE!
Morning Musume。 23's Sei Fukumura and
and Takarin Yonemura of Ocha-no-Ma will be presenting "Halo! STE, presented by Sei FUKUMURA of Morning Musume。
Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year. Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year!
Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year.
As a member of Halo!
I'm so happy to be able to sing, dance and deliver
I'm so happy to be able to sing and dance
I'm really happy to be able to sing, dance and deliver a performance to my fans.
This time, we will be performing songs from the 25 years of Hello! Project's 25 years of music videos
Project's 25 years of songs, we would like to introduce some music videos
Project's 25 years of music videos that we have watched over and over again.
The music video I've watched over and over again is
Risa Niigaki's
This song is "Egao ni Nada Tears Thank you dear my friends" by Risa Niigaki.
This song is a solo song that was shot when Risa Niigaki was graduating
It's a solo song that was shot when Niigaki-san was graduating.
It's a very important song for Niigaki-san, too.
I wanted to cover it, and that's how it all started.
Is that right?
Yes, that's right.
And in the music video
In the music video, there's a bar of photos with the members.
And in the music video, there was a scene where you are looking back at the photos of you and the members.
It was very impressive.
I was also feeling very sad.
I was suppressing my loneliness while watching it.
I was already a member, the same member.
Look at Eliezora.
I felt like, "Thank you very much, Niigaki-san.
With a great feeling.
I remember watching it over and over again
I wonder if I'll ever stop caring about it for a day.
The lady at the store I ended up at, that road...
And the passageway at the train station where I told her I was in love with her just once.
I'll see you again. I'm sure I'll see you again.I'll see you again I'll see you again
Smile again, I'll see you again
Hey, guys, words don't change what I'm saying. It's a promise.
Adorama would have a scene like this...
Yeah, we all cry together, but...
But this is really making me cry.
It's true, isn't it? Smiles and tears
Hey, guys, words can't change the promise
Hello! Hello!
Now, this is a music video that I, Kirara Yonemura, have seen many times... for the song "Living Alone in the City" by Cute.
The A melody of this song is filmed in one cut, and I love it so much that I watched it over and over again even before I joined the trainee program.
I had seen it many times before I became a trainee, but after I actually started to shoot the music video, I felt that it must have been very hard work.
I've come to think that it must have been a lot of work since I actually got to shoot the music video.
My personal favorite part is Airi Suzuki's cute facial expression, which I always pay attention to.
We need to be respectable.
The national government is now a C-oriented organization.
Subtle.
Love in junior high school
I miss it.
The pain... It was so cute.
Why not?
It's my life after all.
I can't see it, even if you're against it.
Why not?
I've tried to imagine a circle-hunting romance.
But it still doesn't feel right.
Is everything alright?
Hello! Hello, Ste!
Hello! Upside down
Upside down
Upside down Everybody's an enemy
Upside down Everybody's a friend
Upside down Who's with me, I want to stand out
More than me Ice tight
I wanna be a kid
Be with me Ice Tight
Free to go on sale
Feel and be with me
I don't want him to see me cry
He's my favorite guy
I don't care what it takes
We've talked about it
I'm not waiting six months.
I don't care if it's a year from now.
Soon, soon, soon, soon.
I want to flap my wings.
Do you know?
Hey! Do you know?
A life for myself
I don't need anybody's permission.
Take it, take it, take it.
I decide.
Me. Yeah. Me.
Do you know?
Up and down. Sometimes it's good.
Up and down. Sometimes it's bad.
Assumptown's got talent.
It's not just Assentown
Mauvaire Aluminum
No weapons, no weapons, no weapons
Mauvais Almi
You're the only one who can't lose
REPEASABLE
As much as you've done in Assentown
REPEASIBLE
Assentown, turn it into you.
The day he first spoke to me
He was the lonely hole in my chest
GO!
Filled the hole in my lonely heart
Retention.
Don't give it up
Audience
Captive
Happiness
I'm a hero
Coming SoonImmediately
Immediately
I want to shine.
Do you know?
Hey!
If you say you're ready, you're ready.
If you put pressure on them, they'll be relentless.
The enemy, the enemy, the enemy.
Me, me, me. Do you know?
I'll be honest with whoever I want.
I'll be honest with you.
I'm not waiting six months.
I don't care if it's a year from now.
Soon, soon, soon
I want to flap my wings
Do you know?
Hey! Do you know?
A life for myself
I don't need anybody's permission
That's it. That's it.
I decide.
Me.
Come on, me. Do you know?
Let's do our best tomorrow.
Morning Musume。 23's Sei Fukumura and Kirara Yonemura of Ochanouma are presenting Halo! STE, presented by Sei FUKUMURA of Morning Musume。
It's time for us to say goodbye, so here's an announcement.
Hello Project 2023 Spring City Circuit is now underway!
Morning Musume。 23 will perform in Miyagi on April 29th and Osaka on May 3rd!
And on April 30, I will be performing at the Rocking On Presents Japan Jam 2023.
This will be my first performance in a year, so I will do my best to give you another exciting stage performance this year!
Ochanouma Concert Tour 2023 Spring Growing Up will start on May 3!
This will be the second tour for Ochanouma, so all 10 of us will do our best!
And on May 10th, Ochanouma's first video work "Ochanouma First Live Tour" will be released!
Ochanouma's first live tour 2022 Start Dash will be released on Blu-ray on May 10!
Please come and see Ochanouma's beautiful performance!
And on May 17th, Morning Musume。 22 25th Anniversary Concert Tour
The Blu-ray and DVD of "Singing to the Beat: Graduation Special at Kagakai" will be released on May 17!
This is the last performance of the 13-member group, and it's going to be a hot one, so please get it!
The "Hello! Project members will be appearing more and more on this channel. New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
We're still in the midst of a difficult time, but let's get through it together! This time, we'll be talking with Sei Fugumura of Morning Musume。 23's Sei FUKUMURA and
This time I'm going to talk with Sei Fukumura of Morning Musume'23 and Kirara Yonemura of Tea No Mame.